through the
surgery it's the reason I wake up every
morning
City difficult for us
surgery was successful but the next
morning I received a
call the next day the bill is already
33.5
so is not a small money and the company
only cover about 20K so I have to come
up from my own pocket money 133.5k that
is big money for
me go through the
surgery income except for work and
insurance so I remember that I had uh
subscrib to insurance by tele marketing
calling me so I dig back all the credit
card bills that's how I found that I
have Sun Life insurance
coverage I get in touch Sun Life through
customer
service all the
GU everything through and then after two
weeks
previously
insurance so I think insurance is a must
to
[Music]
everyone